I think I'm going to go with the
chicken piccata instead of the Cornish game hen.
But now, is there going to be a
vegetarian option, you know, for me?
Yes, definitely.
Oh, great.
What is it?
Dancing.
Hey.
Hey, uh, Mom, I saw the Porsche parked
out front.
Can I get the keys?
Thought I'd take that bad boy out for
a little spin.
Wait a minute.
You let Ross drive the Porsche, and when
I ask you, you say you're the only
one who's allowed to drive it.
Yeah, well, he's my brother.
And plus, he drives so slow, he could
never hurt it.
It's a car, Monica, not a rocket ship.
Whatever, Ross.
Just replace the bulbs and the brake lights
after you're done.
Hey.
Saw the Porsche out there, Mom.
Looking good.
When do I get to take that baby
out again?
You let Joey drive it?
I've never driven it, okay?
Not once.
Okay, once.
Okay, I drive it all the time.
Nice work, everybody.
So much for the, you know, you can
drive it, but don't tell Rachel plan.
Wow, can't believe you lied to me.
Okay, I can fix this.
Okay, Monica, Rachel thinks all you can talk
about is the wedding.
There, okay, I've blown both your secrets, now
we're even.
Well, Rachel, the reason why I won't let
you drive the Porsche is because you're a
terrible driver.
There, that wasn't about the wedding.
Well, great, if you want to go for
a ride in the Porsche, I'll be glad
to take you for a quick spin around
the block.
Yeah, you got a couple hours?
The job's a joke, you're broke, your love
life's D.O.A. It's like you're always
stuck in second gear.
When it hasn't been your day, week, month,
or year.
But I'll be there for you.
So baby, won't you?
Woo, that was a brisk ride.
Take the top down, did you?
Only way to fly.
Come on, Ross, give me the keys.
Monica does not know what she's talking about,
I'm an excellent driver.
You're fast and irresponsible, that adds up to
a bad driver.
Well, in high school, that added up to
head cheerleader.
Did you see the look that girl just
gave me, huh?
She must have seen me cruising in the
bad boy.
I think she's checking out your beehive, Ross.
What?
Give me a brush.
Give me the keys.
No way.
Well, no brush.
Fine, you know what, it doesn't matter.
Because, if I remember correctly, there is a
comb on the floor of the bathroom.
Tanner, we still haven't gotten an RSVP from
your dad.
Oh, right.
Maybe that's because I didn't send him an
invitation.
Why not?
An invitation, that's like almost asking him to
come.
Tanner, he's your father.
He should be at our wedding.
I was going to send him an invitation,
but then I took a look at the
stamp.
It was one of those Marilyn Monroe stamps.
And I thought, my dad has that dress.
Wow.
That must be a very different view when
he stands over an air vent.
I should see him singing Happy Birthday, Mr.
President.
We have to invite him.
I don't even know the man, okay?
We're not that close.
I haven't seen him in years.
What are you going to do when he
finds out he wasn't even asked?
Well, he doesn't have to know.
It's not like we run in the same
circles.
I hang out with you guys, and he...
Stars in a drag show in Vegas.
Oh, I think I want to trade circles.
Trust me, you don't want him there either,
okay?
Nobody's going to be staring at the bride
when the father of the groom is wearing
a backless dress.
So what?
As long as he's not wearing a white
dress and a veil, I don't care.
Okay, I think I need to do some
shopping.
Ah.
Ooh, nice.
Ah!
My God!
What do you think you're doing?
Just washing the windshield.
There is no way I am letting you
drive this car.
Couldn't find the comb?
No.
So why don't you just hand over the
keys?
Oh.
Well, I...
Do not start this car.
Okay, okay.
I will give you 20 bucks if you
get out of this car right now.
Look.
Ross, if you're so freaked out, just get
in the car.
With you?
Yeah, right.
All right.
Okay, okay, okay.
What are you doing?
Get in the front.
In the death seat?
Oh.
Hey, guys.
Hey, sweetie.
Ready to go?
Yeah, sure.
Ooh, I left my purse up at Monica's.
I'll be right back.
Wait a minute.
What?
Oh.
Ooh.
Uh-oh.
That one kept going.
So, you and Phoebe, huh?
How long you been going out?
Over a month.
Wow.
Oh.
Maybe you and I ought to get to
know each other a little better.
Sure.
I'd like that.
Yeah.
So, uh...
What's your name?
It's Jake.
Joey.
Hey, Jake.
Do you like the Knicks?
Yeah, big fan.
Me, too.
There's a game on Tuesday.
You want to go?
Yeah, that'd be great.
Let me make sure I'm not doing anything
Tuesday.
Here.
What's this?
It's your suitcase.
We're going to Las Vegas.
Are you serious?
You mean like a loping?
No more stupid wedding stuff?
No more these flowers or these flowers or
these flowers?
Think of the money we'll save.
We're not loping.
I love the flowers.
Can our wedding be bigger, please?
We're going to Las Vegas to see your
dad.
It's time you two talked, and I want
to get to know my father-in-law.
You already went over this, and I won.
No, you didn't.
Oh, and honey, just so you know, now
that you're marrying me, you don't get to
win anymore.
Look, forget it, okay?
I don't want to go.
I don't want to see him.
I don't want him.
Taylor, look, I know that your dad embarrassed
you.
I know...
No, no, no.
All kids are embarrassed by their parents.
You'd have to come up with a whole
new word for what I went through.
When I was in high school, he used
to come to all of my swim meets
dressed as a different Hollywood starlet.
It was hard enough to be 14.
You're skinny.
You're wearing Speedos that your mom promised you
would grow into.
And you look up into the stands, and
there's your dad cheering you on, dressed as
Carmen Miranda.
He's wearing a headdress with real fruit that
he will later hand out to your friends
as a healthy snack.
But he was there.
My dad didn't come to one of my
brownie meetings.
You were in brownie?
No, I ate them.
Hey, look, the point is that he was
at every one of your swim meets, and
he was there cheering you on.
Okay, that's a pretty great dad.
He had sex with Mr. Garibaldi.
Who's Mr. Garibaldi?
Does it matter?
Chandler, you're not 14 anymore, okay?
Maybe it's time that you let that stuff
go.
If your father's not at your wedding, you're
gonna regret it for the rest of your
life.
Yeah, oh, okay.
But I'm just doing this for you.
Yes!
So I really never get to win anymore?
I don't want you to ever really win
before.
Hey.
Listen, you know how, uh, when you're wearing
pants and you lean forward, I check out
your underwear?
Yeah.
Well, when Jake did it, I saw that
he was wearing women's underwear.
I know, they were mine.
Oh.
No, no, wait, that's weird.
No, it's not.
We were just goofing around, and I dared
him to try them on.
That's weird.
I'm wearing his briefs right now.
That's kind of hot.
I think so, too.
And that little flap, great for holding my
lipstick.
Yeah, I wouldn't know about that.
Yeah, you know, Jake says that women's underwear
is actually more comfortable.
And he loves the way the silk feels
against his skin.
Yeah, well, next thing you know, he'll be
telling you that your high heels are good
for his posture.
There is nothing wrong with Jake, okay?
He is all man.
I'm thinking even more than you.
Oh, yeah, he looked like a real lumberjack
in those pink laces.
I'm just saying that only a man completely
secure with his masculinity could walk around in
women's underwear.
I don't think you could ever do that.
Hey, I am secure with my masculinity.
Okay, whatever.
You've seen my huge stack of porn, right?
Here you go.
Thanks.
Look all you want, there's nothing there.
Slow down or I am returning to the
back seat.
Would you calm down?
No, no, you're driving 15 miles over the
speed limit.
I am driving five miles over the limit.
They raised it by ten.
What, are they crazy?
God, I forgot how much I love driving.
I have got to get my license renewed.
You don't have a valid driver's license?
Okay, that is it.
Pull over right now.
Oh, Ross, you're so tense.
You've just got to relax, okay?
You just need to relax, all right?
You just need to relax.
What are you doing?
Are you okay?
That's not funny.
Just stop horsing around.
I am not horsing around, okay?
I am porching around.
Uh-oh.
Okay, stay calm.
Nothing's going to happen to you.
You are not in that much trouble.
Really?
You think so?
I was talking to myself.
You're going down.
Has someone taken your order yet?
Oh, yeah, she did.
Uh, he did.
She did?
I'm sorry, I'm new.
I don't...
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, I just ordered a beer.
They're straight.
I get it.
I'd still say that if we had called
your dad, we could have gotten better seats.
No, no, I don't want him to know
we're here yet.
I'm not sure if I'm ready for that.
And besides, he's not going to be too
happy to see me either.
Why not?
I don't know if I've told you this,
but he's kind of tried to get in
contact with me a lot over the last
few years.
What?
Yeah.
He's made phone calls, written letters, even came
to New York.
But I always said I was too busy
to see him.
You know, it's all very cats in the
cradle.
I don't want to get into it.
Here we go.
Ladies and gentlemen, please welcome the incomparable Helena
Handbasket!
Hello, Tony.
And there's Daddy.
Switch places with me.
Come on, I'll go under and you go
over.
Yeah, I'll get right on that.
Come on, boss.
No, hey, Rach, come on.
Come on.
Yeah, I'm sure we won't get arrested for
this.
Oh, God.
Hi, officer.
Is I going a little too fast?
Oh, my God.
Can I see your license, please?
Oh, yes, absolutely.
You know, it's weird, but I had a
dream last night that I was stopped by
a policeman.
And then he, uh...
Well, I probably shouldn't tell you the rest.
He gave you a big, fat ticket?
Your license?
Yes.
Here you go.
Officer, uh...
Handsome?
It's Hanson.
Oh, I'm sorry.
My mistake.
Dear Lord.
Wow.
Here it comes.
This is a great picture.
Oh, really?
You think so?
You know, I had just rolled right out
of bed.
Yeah, well, you look phenomenal.
Well, she should.
It was taken ten years ago.
You know what?
You're probably, um...
Probably wondering about the old date.
Yes, I am.
You're an Aquarius, huh?
I bet you're a Gemini.
Nope.
Taurus?
No.
Virgo?
Nope.
Sagittarius?
Yep.
I knew it!
Well, I'll tell you what.
Yeah?
You're not gonna speed anymore, right?
I won't speed.
And you promise you'll get this taken care
of right away?
I promise.
And in the meantime, you better let him
drive.
Does he have a license?
Yeah.
Can he handle the stick?
Uh, well...
I can handle a stick!
I feel pretty, oh, so pretty.
I feel pretty and witty and...
Hey!
That can't be your father.
Believe me, I've been saying that for years.
Oh, my God.
What?
That's Mr. Garibaldi playing the piano.
Oh, I'm loved by a pretty, wonderful boy
Hello, and welcome to the show.
I see some of our regulars in the
audience.
And a couple of irregulars.
She's coming into the audience.
Relax, you'll be fine.
Oh, much better.
You're invisible now.
And where are you from?
Bakersfield.
I'm sorry?
No, no, I heard.
I'm just sorry.
Oh, look, a standing ovation already.
So early in the show.
Oh, turn around.
Let me see your pretty face.
Can we have our drinks, please?
Waiter, Tris.
Hey, Pheebs.
Hey.
Check it out.
Huh?
How much of a man am I?
Oh, nice.
Manly and also kind of a slut.
You know, I'm beginning to see what Jake
was talking about.
Uh-huh.
The silk feels really good.
Yeah, and things aren't as smashed down as
I thought they were going to be.
It's great, Joe.
Yeah, and you have so many more choices
than you do with men's underwear.
Bikini, French cut, thong.
And the fabrics.
You got cotton, silk, lace.
And you know what I've always wondered about?
Pantyhose.
You know, the way they start at your
toe and then they go all the way
up to your...
I should go take these off, shouldn't I?
I think it's important that you do.
So what's your name?
Chandler.
What an unusual name.
You must have had terribly fascinating parents.
Oh, they're a hoot.
And who is your friend?
I'm Monica.
Monica.
Where are you from?
New York.
I'm not very fond of New York.
Queens I like.
Ooh.
Ooh, what is this?
Sparkling, something, honey, huh?
Actually, Monica and I are engaged.
Really?
Congratulations.
When's the big day?
In two weeks.
I see.
Well, I wish you both a lifetime of
happiness.
So, you're bald.
Wait.
We'd really love it if you could be
there.
Really?
I know it would make me happy.
Ma'am.
And I wouldn't miss it for the world.
Ooh, I'm getting all misty here.
You'd think I was having my legs waxed
or something.
You okay?
Yeah.
Thanks for making me do this.
Before we go on with the show, I
just want to say to the bride and
groom how lucky they are to have you.
You two have found each other.
In every life, a little rain must fall.
Fortunately, in my life, it's raining men.
It's raining men.
When I was growing up, I played the
one on the far left.
Oh!
I think you've had enough fun for today.
You know what?
Remind me to introduce you to someone.
Who?
Fourth Gear.
What?
What does he want?
I wasn't doing anything.
Well, maybe he saw your hand slip briefly
from the ten and two o'clock position.
Maybe it's Sergeant Sagittarius coming back to flirt
some more.
Perhaps he didn't tarnish the badge enough.
It's a different guy.
Good evening, officer.
Do you know how fast you were traveling
back there?
Uh, no, I don't, but it could not
have been more than 60.
You're right.
It was 37.
Really?
May I see your license, please?
You're kidding, right?
I mean, you're not going to give me
a ticket for driving too slow, are you?
That's right.
You want to help me out here?
Sorry, what?
Can you do the thing that you did
before?
Oh, yeah, I don't think so.
I don't...
I don't think I want to tarnish his
badge.
You know, officer, I, um...
I had the weirdest dream last night.
Your license, please.
You don't...
You don't want to hear about my dream?
Officer Petty?
It's Petty.
I'll be right back with your ticket.
Okay.
You have a son.
I know, I know.
Feel better?
Yeah, much.
Listen, uh, not that I'm, you know, insecure
about my manhood or anything, you know, but,
uh, I think I need to hook up
with a woman like right now.
Yeah, I understand.
Yeah, okay.
Hey, hi.
Hi.
You look familiar.
Do I know you from somewhere?
I don't think so.
Oh, maybe it's because I'm on television.
I'm an actor on Days of Our Lives.
Wow, really?
Mm-hmm.
$4.50, please.
Oh, let me get this.
These are for you.
Oh, my God.